Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Working Agreements and Related Correspondence, Series 1
  - Minneapolis Fruit and Produce Industry, 1967-1984; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Minneapolis Household Goods Movers Association, Incorporated [1/3], 1967-1982; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis Household Goods Movers Association, Incorporated [2/3], 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Minneapolis Household Goods Movers Association, Incorporated [3/3], 1973-1982; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Minneapolis Mountain Foods, 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Minneapolis Transfermen's Association, 1958-1961; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Minneapolis Van and Warehouse Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Minneopa Concrete Products Company, 1969-1992; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota Boxed Meat, 1987; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Express, 1979-1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Minnesota Express, Willmar, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota-Wisconsin Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1978; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota-Wisconsin, Ward Transfer Warehouse Division, 1976-1982; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mix Transfer Company, 1978; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Modern Express, Incorporated, 1985; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mohawk Transfer and Storage Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery Ward and Company, Incorporated [1/2], 1975-1979; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery Ward and Company, Incorporated [2/2], 1980-1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Morrell Transfer, Incorporated, 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Morton Frozen Foods, 1973-1984; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Moving and Storage Industry of New York, 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Murphy Delivery Service, Incorporated, 1978-1985; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Murphy Motor Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1975-1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Murphy Motor Freight, Shamrock Division, 1978-1985; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Murphy Rigging and Erecting, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Murphy Tank Service Company, 1964-1967; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Murphy Warehouse Company [1/4], 1971-1978; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Murphy Warehouse Company [2/4], 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Murphy Warehouse Company [3/4], 1981-1984; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Murphy Warehouse Company [4/4], 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Musingwear, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - National Automobile Transporters Agreement [1/3], 1973-1982; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - National Automobile Transporters Agreement [2/3], 1981-1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - National Automobile Transporters Agreement [3/3], 1976-1987; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - National Master Cement Agreement, 1967-1976; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - National Construction Agreement, 1980-1983; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - National Drivers, Incorporated, 1974-1975; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National Food Stores, Incorporated, 1964-1973; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Master Freight Agreement [1/4], 1969-1979; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement [2/4], 1980-1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement [3/4], 1986-1998; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement [4/4], 1969-1988; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - National Master Freight and Monetary Proposal, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - National Master and Supplemental Freight Agreements [1/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - National Master and Supplemental Freight Agreements [2/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - National Master and Supplemental Freight Agreements [3/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - National Super Markets, Incorporated, 1976-1982; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Tea Company [1/2], 1963-1967; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Tea Company [2/2], 1970-1986; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - National Warehouses, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Neptune World Wide Moving, Incorporated, 1979-1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Neuendorf Transportation Company, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - New Ulm Concrete Products, Incorporated, 1990-1997; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - New Ulm Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - New Ulm Memorial Foundation, Incorporated (Highland Manor) [1/4], 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - New Ulm Memorial Foundation, Incorporated (Highland Manor) [2/4], 1992-1994; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - New Ulm Memorial Foundation, Incorporated (Highland Manor) [3/4], 1994-1997; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - New Ulm Memorial Foundation, Incorporated (Highland Manor) [4/4], 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - New Ulm Wholesale, Incorporated, 1983-1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Nordby Transfer, 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Norman G. Jensen, Incorporated [1/3], 1978-1979; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Norman G. Jensen, Incorporated [2/3], 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Norman G. Jensen, Incorporated [3/3], 1978; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - North American Van Lines, Incorporated, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - North Star Concrete Company [1/3], 1972-1993; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - North Star Concrete Company [2/3], 1993-1999; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - North Star Concrete Company [3/3], 1963-1966; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - North Star Warehouse, Incorporated [1/2], 1975-1990; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - North Star Warehouse, Incorporated [2/2], 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Northeast Produce Distributor, 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Northern Cargo Association, 1979-1986; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Northern Cryogenics, Incorporated, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Northern Tank Line, 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Airlines, Incorporated, 1973-1974; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Delivery Service, 1980; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Northwest Produce Company, Incorporated, 1979-1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Northwest Transfer and Warehouse, Incorporated, 1982; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Northwest Transport Service, Incorporated, 1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Northwest Warehousemen's Association [1/2], 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Northwest Warehousemen's Association [2/2], 1961-1982; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - OCHS Brick and Tile Company [1/5], 1977-1983; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - OCHS Brick and Tile Company [2/5], 1983-1993; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - OCHS Brick and Tile Company [3/5], 1993-1996; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - OCHS Brick and Tile Company [4/5], 1996-2004; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - OCHS Brick and Tile Company [5/5], 1961-1964; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - O'Brien Corporation, 1978-1979; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated, 1997-2002; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Olund Transfer, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Our Own Hardware Company, 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Gamble Robinson Company, 1978-1984; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.), 1979-1988; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Redi Mix and C.H. Gould Companies, 1976-1983; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Pazik Enterprises, Incorporated, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Peck's Produce, 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Pennant Food Company (Van Den Bergh Foods Company), 1993-1998; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Pepsi-Cola (7-Up Bottling Company), 1978-2000; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Perkins Motor Transport Company, 1962-1964; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Perlman Rocque Company (North), 1981-1985; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Perry W. Myers, Incorporated, 1979-1988; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Pipe Line Contractors Association, 1981-1992; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Pillsbury Company [1/2], 1974-1988; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Pillsbury Company [2/2], 1973-1977; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Poly-Tech Division of U.S. Industries Corporation, 1972-1975; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Preferred Products, Incorporated, 1972-1982; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Prepared Foods International Division of Fresh Pack [1/2], 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Prepared Foods International Division of Fresh Pack [2/2], 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Quickie Transport Company, 1964-1988; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Quinn Transfer Company, 1964-1982; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Rapidways Truck Leasing, 1964-1988; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Raymond Motor Transportation Company, Incorporated, 1974; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Ready Mixed Concrete Company, 1961-1964; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated [1/3], 1967-1980; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated [2/3], 1979-1988; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated [3/3], 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Redi Mix, 1961-1964; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Ringsby United Freight Lines, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Roadway Express, Incorporated, 1981-1991; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Rochester Bread Bakery, 1969-1972; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Rochester Materials Company, 1989-1994; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Ruan Transport, 1964-1985; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - S.A.L. Cartage, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Salt Creek Freightways, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Trail Transportation/ BN Transport, 1985; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Seeco, Incorporated, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [1/6], 1973-1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [2/6], 1984-1993; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [3/6], 1993-1999; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [4/6], 1999-2002; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [5/6], 2002-2004; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Shari Candies, Incorporated [6/6], 1965-1970; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Shulman Air Freight [1/2], 1973-1979; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Shulman Air Freight [2/2], 1973-1978; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Six Transfer, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Skellet Van and Storage Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Skelly Oil Company, 1968-1970; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Smith's Transfer Corporation, 1976-1987; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Soderstrom Transfer, Incorporated, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Southern Minnesota Construction Company, 1996-1999; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Space Center Minnesota, Incorporated, 1972-1985; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Spartech Plastics [1/4], 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Spartech Plastics [2/4], 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Spartech Plastics [3/4], 1993-1999; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Spartech Plastics [4/4], 1999-2005; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Spring Air, 1973; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - State Distributing Company, 1993-1997; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Stemm Transfer and Storage Company, 1976-1985; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Sterling Cartage Company, 1974-1985; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Stinar Corporation [1/2], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Stinar Corporation [2/2], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [1/3], 1965-1978; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [2/3], 1978-1984; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [3/3], 1971-1984; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Super Valu Stores, Incorporated, 1976-1984; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Superior Concrete Block Company, Incorporated [1/3], 1972-1990; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Superior Concrete Block Company, Incorporated [2/3], 1990-1998; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Superior Concrete Block Company, Incorporated [3/3], 1969-1972; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Superior Dairies Fresh Milk Company [1/2], 1975-1990; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Superior Daries Fresh Milk Company [2/2], 1966-1972; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Swift Dairy and Poultry Company [1/2], 1975-1979; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Swift Dairy and Poultry Company [2/2], 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Swiftlines, Incorporated, 1975-1988; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Team Central Company, Incorporated [1/2], 1974-1986; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Team Central Company, Incorporated [2/2], 1974-1980; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Texgas Corporation, 1974-1984; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Toll Company, 1983-1990; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Tooltech, Incorporated, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Totino's Finer Food, Incorporated, 1973; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Tow Distributing Corporation, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Town and Country Foods, Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tracy Bottling Company, Incorporated, 1972-1986; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Transfer and Trucking Agreements, 1973-1977; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Transpersonnel, Incorporated, 1973-1983; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Trucking, Incorporated, 1980-1988; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Trucking Employers, Incorporated, 1969-1978; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Trucking Management, Incorporated, 1978; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Trucking Management, Incorporated/ Regional Carriers, Incorporated, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Turf Rite, Incorporated, 1983; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Twin City Concrete Company [1/2], 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Twin City Concrete Company [2/2], 1977-1978; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Twin City Freight, Incorporated, 1988; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Twin City Produce Supplies, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Tyson Truck Lines, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - United Buckingham Freight Lines, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [1/7], 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [2/7], 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [3/7], 1985-1989; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [4/7], 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [5/7], 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [6/7], 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - United Foods, Incorporated [7/7], 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - United Foods, Incorporated, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - United Van Bus Delivery [1/2], 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - United Van Bus Delivery [2/2], 1972-1975; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - United Van Bus Delivery, Marathon Division, 1984-1990; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - United Warehouse, 1979; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - University of Minnesota, 1987-1991; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Uptown Transfer Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Van Den Bergh Foods Company (Aldons, Golden Pantry) [1/2], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Van Den Bergh Foods Company (Aldons, Golden Pantry) [2/2], 1990-1995; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Van Voorst Trucking, Incorporated, 1978-1988; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Volk Transfer, 1975; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Waldoch Freight Transfer, 1964-1979; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Wallner Construction Company [1/3], 1961-1989; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Wallner Construction Company [2/3], 1990-1996; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wallner Construction Company [3/3], 1963-1965; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Ward Transfer, Incorporated, 1976; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Warehouse Service Company, 1967-1979; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Watsonville Employers Frozen Food Association, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Wessin Gorman, Incorporated, 1973-1974; Series (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Western Mineral Products, 1952-1961; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Whittaker Corporation, 1974-1977; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wholesale Bakeries, 1982-1994; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Wholesale Plumbing Group, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Wholesale Produce Supply Company, 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Winona Van Norman Division of Hein-Werner, 1980-1989; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Wis-Pak, Incorporated, 1987-2005 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - World Wide, Incorporated, 1970-1982; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Worthington Redi Mix, 1966-1987; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Worthington Regional Hospital [1/4], 1975-1984; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Worthington Regional Hospital [2/4], 1984-1990; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Worthington Regional Hospital [3/4], 1990-1998; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Worthington Regional Hospital [4/4], 1997-2001; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Yellow Freight Systems, Incorporated, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Zuccaro's Produce, 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Grievance Records, Series 2
  This series is divided into two subseries for grievance committee agendas and minutes and individual company records. Folder titles are arranged alphabetically by committee or company.
  The materials of this series include the agendas and minutes for different grievance committees, with the bulk coming from the Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee, Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee, and Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee. Grievance records and associated correspondence from individual companies are also included in this series. They range in date from 1963-2009. These materials document the proceedings and decisions of grievance hearings and the individual complaints.
  - Grievance Committee agendas and minutes, Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Chicago Joint Area Committee Grievance Hearings, 1967-1970; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Furniture Grievance, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Grocery Grievance Committee, 1971-1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Joint Cartage Grievance Committee [1/3], 1970-1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Joint Cartage Grievance Committee [2/3], 1980-1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Joint Cartage Grievance Committee [3/3], 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee, 1968-1969; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1970; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1970; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1971; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1971; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1972; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1972; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1973; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1973; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/4], 1974; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/4], 1974; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/4], 1974; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/4], 1974; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/5], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/5], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/5], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/5], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [5/5], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/4], 1976; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/4], 1976; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/4], 1976; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/4], 1976; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/4], 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/4], 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/4], 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/4], 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1978; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1978; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/3], 1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/3], 1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/3], 1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1980; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1980; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/3], 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/3], 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/3], 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/3], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/3], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/3], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/5], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/5], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/5], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/5], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [5/5], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/4], 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/4], 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/4], 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [4/4], 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)